{
    "id": "1823838daa884422a8369d75b88fa03d",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I think I will be staying here for ……………………… more days.",
            "description": "A few indicates a small number few means almost none. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is junior ……………………….. me.",
            "description": "The words junior, senior, superior and inferior are followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The exam was ………………………… than I thought.",
            "description": "Easier is the comparative form of easy.",
            "answers": [
                "easier",
                "more easy",
                "more easier"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………………… than me.",
            "description": "Cleverer is the comparative form of clever. ",
            "answers": [
                "cleverer",
                "more clever",
                "more cleverer"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Please wait …………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Take ……………………………. of the two routes.",
            "description": "When the comparison is between two people or things, the comparative form is preferred. ",
            "answers": [
                "the short",
                "the shorter",
                "the shortest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………………… of the three brothers.",
            "description": "When the comparison is among more than two people or things, the superlative form is used. ",
            "answers": [
                "the smart",
                "the smarter",
                "the smartest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………………… than you.",
            "description": "Much can modify comparatives. More cannot modify comparatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "much young",
                "more younger",
                "much younger"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t earn as much as ……………………………..",
            "description": "Object pronouns are preferred after as and than.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Man is ……………………………… intelligent animal.",
            "description": "Use the with superlatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "the most",
                "the more"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "English is widely …………………………….. in India.",
            "description": "In passive structures use the third form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "spoken",
                "spoke",
                "speak"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I love you more than ………………………………",
            "description": "Object pronouns are preferred after as and than. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}